Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
[♪ legendary music playing]
[lightsaber activates]
[♪ music fades]
[♪ theme music playing]
[beeping]
[Gramps] Huh?
There's no need to worry. okay?
We're heading straight for Bibin.
just as the Margrave directed.
I'm not worried with all the experience
you have. old-timer.
[Gramps] Oh? [laughs]
-[whirring]
-[lightsaber buzzing]
[Kara breathes deeply]
[grunts]
-[lasers firing]
-[grunting]
-[clangs]
[Juro] That's enough.
[panting]
Your mind is elsewhere right now.
Focus and be in the moment.
[Juro sighs]
Something is troubling you.
Tell me what it is.
[Kara] When we were on Makoma Ko.
the man we met...
The one named Gennoh...
he had a red lightsaber.
I was just wondering
if it is possible that my father. he...
made that red lightsaber.
Hmm. There is an old Jedi tale...
-Huh?
-[Juro] Of course.
you wouldn't have heard it.
A long time ago. our former Master
once tried to revive the Jedi Order
to bring about peace in the galaxy.
Just as darkness
is born wherever there is light.
so emerged those who used the Force
to bring about selfishness and greed.
They were called the Sith.
That lightsaber he wielded
could have been one
handed down from long ago.
So. then my father might not have made it.
[chuckles]
The one thing I know about Zhima
is that he's the type of man
who would not aid a Sith.
even if his life depended on it.
[sighs]
I believe you.
but something still seems off. Juro.
I have a bad feeling about this.
Juro. I need to see my father.
We have to find him as soon as possible.
Trust me. I understand how you feel.
Nevertheless. facing Nawaam alone
would not be a smart decision.
We need more Jedi.
We need soldiers
who will be willing to fight alongside us.
[sighs]
[Juro chuckles]
[gasps]
Kara. you have a strong connection
to the Force.
Trust in the Force.
and listen to your heart.
And when the time is right. we will know.
[Kara] Hmm.
[digital beeping]
-[Kara gasps]
-[Juro] Hmm?
[Homen over comms] Juro.
please come to the bridge.
We'll be exiting hyperspace shortly.
[♪ captivating music playing]
Whoa. [gasps]
[gasps] It's huge...
[Homen] There it is.
I've always dreamed
of stepping foot on Bibin.
-How come?
-[Homen] Hmm?
[sighs] Let's just say. this place.
it's special to us.
-A long time ago...
-[Kara gasps]
...there was a Jedi who. on his own.
founded a small order there.
And it was there on Bibin
where I studied the Force.
As did your father.
It was where he became a Jedi.
[Kara gasps]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[surveillance droid beeping and chirping]
[ships whooshing]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[Four-Nines chirps]
[whirring. clicking]
[Four-Nines whirring]
[quietly] Hurry it up. will ya?
[Four-Nines speaking Droid]
[in English] Wait. what?
You think I was spooked
by seeing Nawaam's lightsaber?
[chuckles] No way. Not in the least.
[gasps]
Kyber crystals?
[Four-Nines speaking Droid]
[in English] What do you think
they're doing with so many of them?
What could they be planning? [grunts]
[Four-Nines speaking Droid]
[steam hissing]
[ship powering up]
[machinery whirring]
[♪ suspenseful music continues]
-[Ethan grunts]
-[Four-Nines whirring]
[mechanical whirring]
[Gennoh] I beg your forgiveness.
General Nawaam.
I failed to capture Juro.
I am prepared to accept your punishment.
[Nawaam] I have no intention
to punish the last of the Sith.
You will have your opportunity
to face Juro again and stop him next time.
[Gennoh] I'm sorry. but... it wasn't him.
It was Lah Zhima's daughter
who got in my way.
[Nawaam] Oh?
[Gennoh] I sensed that the Force
is strong with her.
The sooner we defeat her. the better.
[mechanical whirring]
[Gennoh] Who could have thought
they could be used this way?
[Nawaam] I can think of no better way
than to use this symbol
to show the galaxy our power.
[Four-Nines speaking Droid]
[In English] They're using the crystals
to make a weapon?
[weapon powering up]
[electronic beeping]
[♪ sinister music playing]
[beeping continues]
[Ethan gasps]
[weapon powering up]
-[alarm beeping]
-[Nawaam] Huh?
-[electricity crackling]
-[all gasping]
[scientists screaming]
[weapon powering down]
[scientists groaning]
I'm sorry. General Nawaam.
but we're still unable to get the crystals
to resonate with the--
-[electricity crackling]
-[wincing]
-[Nawaam] Bring me Lord Zhima.
-[droid beeps]
[breathes heavily]
Well. this is certainly a surprise.
I never expected any Jedi to come
back to this planet. Margrave Juro.
Thank you for granting me an audience.
Lady Tafflah.
We are most grateful that you---
Spare me the pleasantries.
I'm quite busy at the moment.
so please just state your business.
What is it that brings you here?
Uh...
There is a general named Nawaam
who seeks to gain control of the galaxy
and whose influence is rapidly expanding.
I am of the opinion
that this will lead us all to destruction.
As a Jedi. I cannot sit by and do nothing.
[Tafflah sighs]
And so I was guided here.
You were guided here?
You mean guided by the Force?
I'm sorry to say this.
but from my perspective.
-you Jedi seem to be nothing more...
-[gasps]
...than bringers of chaos.
Surely you couldn't have already forgotten
about that incident.
have you. Margrave Juro?
[Kara sighs]
[sighs]
I can't stress how dangerous Nawaam is.
He must be stopped.
[sighs wearily]
Very well. then.
At any rate. I have no desire to further
dwell on the tragedies of the past.
But as you already know.
there are no longer
any Jedi left on our planet.
What we are searching for are allies
who will stand up with us
for the sake of the galaxy.
You are free to conduct your search.
However. keep in mind that our planet
recognizes the sovereignty
of each and every person.
We will land in the mining region.
[Gramps] Alrighty.
[whooshes]
[quietly] Hey. Homen. do you know why
the Jedi Order on this planet dissolved?
And what incident?
[Homen] The story is that the Master who
oversaw the Jedi Order here was killed...
by his own Padawan.
[engine whirring]
[digital beeping]
What's this? There's an asteroid
-that's headed straight for us.
-No. don't worry. We'll be fine.
But...
[Homen and Kara gasp]
[gasps]
[Juro] I can handle it from here.
[♪ mysterious music playing]
[doors whirring]
[gasps] Are you sure that this is safe?
Trust me. Just follow them in.
[Kara grunts] Hmm.
[whooshing]
[thuds]
[ship hisses]
[Kara] Are these the soldiers
we were looking for?
But they're just regular miners. right?
It would seem so. wouldn't it?
Huh?
[♪ tense music playing]
[Kara pants]
[♪ music ends]
[blade slashes]
-[blade clangs]
-[Kara and Homen gasp]
Draw now!
[gasps] Juro!
-[Juro grunts]
-[man grunts]
-[blades clanging]
-[both grunting]
-[Kara gasps]
-[Juro grunts]
[both grunting]
[blades clang]
-[blades clang]
-[whimpers. shudders]
-[man laughs]
-[gasps]
[continues laughing]
Now that's true Jedi mastery
if I've ever seen it.
Not too shabby yourself.
It's nice to see
you haven't gotten rusty. Kwana.
It's been far too long.
You look like you're in good health.
Hey! Everyone. Master Juro
has returned to Bibin!
[miner] Mmm-mmm.
-[Kara gasps]
-[Gramps] Huh?
Sorry about them.
They don't bear you
any ill will or anything.
No worries. It's a natural reaction.
Ever since that incident.
people view the Jedi differently.
It must have been hard for you.
You looked up to Master Reno
more than anyone else I knew.
[Kwana] Oh. my dream of becoming a Jedi
is a thing of the past.
Uh. but speaking of...
would you mind giving me
a peek of your lightsaber. Juro?
[grunts]
I know I probably shouldn't be asking.
but I'm just so proud that my old friend
is now a true Jedi Master.
[lightsaber buzzing]
[gasps]
[Kwana sighs]
[Kara grunts] Hmm?
So. the two of you know each other?
It's a little more than just that.
The two of us.
we spent our youth together.
-We're like brothers.
-[Juro] Hmm.
Kwana. my friend.
I have a favor to ask of you.
It is something that involves
not only you. but the miners.
I can't imagine
what a Jedi would need help with.
I need help stopping a war.
And I seek your aid.
You're speaking of Nawaam.
I've heard tales of his fearsomeness.
[Juro grunts]
[♪ tense music playing]
[Nawaam] What are these for?
[droid] Well. he may not be armed.
but as a prisoner--
[rumbling]
-[Four-Nines speaking Droid]
-[Ethan gasps]
[Nawaam in English] My apologies
for the disrespect. master.
I've told you many times.
I am not your Master. Nawaam.
[Nawaam exhales]
[Ethan] Master?
[electronic beeping]
[low whirring]
Those are kyber crystals.
[weapon powering up]
[electricity crackling]
-[scientists grunting]
-[weapon whirring]
[electricity crackling]
[weapon powering down]
[whirring]
Hmm.
[♪ mysterious music playing]
[whooshes]
[kyber crystals crackling]
-[dings]
-[whooshes]
[electronic beeping]
It's suddenly restabilized.
I don't understand how this happened.
[grunts]
[Nawaam] I expected nothing less. Master.
What you've done
goes against the laws of nature.
If you keep this up.
you will destroy the entire planet.
[Nawaam] That is a device
that will bring about people's awakening.
Once the crystal's light is unleashed.
they will come to realize the truth.
That there is only one thing
needed for peace... and that is strength.
I knew that once I explained.
you would understand. Master.
[grunts]
[droid] Lord Nawaam.
our surveillance satellites
have located the exact location
-of Juro's ship.
-[gasps] Hmm.
[whirring. beeping]
[ships whooshing]
[all laughing]
[♪ lively music playing]
From the looks of things.
this Kwana is quite popular.
Yeah.
-Kara. come with me.
-[Kara] Huh?
-Homen. you should hear this as well.
-[Homen] Hmm?
[lively chatter]
Oh. Juro! Look.
See how many fearless folk have gathered!
Now. tell me how we can help you.
[Juro exhales]
[Juro] Zhima was abducted by Nawaam.
What? Is that really true?
I kept him in hiding on Hy Izlan
where he created a new life for himself
as a sabersmith.
I'm not sure how exactly.
but Nawaam must have caught wind of it
and then abducted him.
No doubt Nawaam wants to use Zhima's
technology in his galactic conquest.
And that is why I must rescue him.
Hmm. I still remember that day.
We were so young. you. me. and him.
We all swore to each other that we would
eventually become Jedi one day.
Back then we called him brother.
And today. he's a wanton criminal.
[both gasp]
Huh?
This girl is Zhima's daughter.
She traveled all this way
to save her father.
Huh? [gasps. stutters]
I don't believe it.
-[Kara] Juro...
-[Kwana] Hmm?
Sorry. but... what was he talking about?
-[Juro] Kara.
-[gasps]
The sad truth is.
your father was exiled from Bibin
as a criminal.
His crime was murdering his master.
Reno Tsutara.
[Kara gasps]
There has to be more to it!
I'm afraid I don't know
the details of what happened.
since I was already
on Hy Izlan at that time.
so I only heard the rumors.
Then one day.
he suddenly appeared before me.
He looked to be in a pitiful state.
He requested that I shelter him
and asked me not to ask any questions.
[Baby Kara crying]
[Juro] In his arms was you as a baby.
-[crying]
-[♪ somber music playing]
[breath trembling]
But Juro. how can you help him
after what he's done?
Our master was killed... by his hand.
I still believe in Zhima.
He must've had his reasons.
And I came here hoping
that you would feel the same way. brother.
[indistinct chatter]
[all laughing]
-[laughing stops]
-[miner] Hmm?
[miners exclaim]
[miners murmuring]
Thank you all for coming today.
My name is Margrave Juro.
I am a Jedi who studied here
under Master Reno Tsutara.
We have witnessed Nawaam's cruelty.
as he sets out to conquer our galaxy.
He has joined forces
with the remaining Sith
and grows his ranks
by recruiting those who only seek power.
There is no faction in the galaxy
capable of resisting Nawaam.
I believe he can still be stopped!
But only if we stand together.
Otherwise. the galaxy
will enter a dark age.
Our future now depends on all of you.
[silence]
[sighs]
Huh?
-[Kwana grunts]
-[Homen gasps]
-[screams]
-[grunts]
[grunting]
-I'm ashamed to even know you cowards!
-[Kara grunts]
-[Kwana grunts]
-[Homen] Ah!
What happened to your backbone?
Since when did you all become
so faint of heart?
[straining. gasps]
[Kwana] The galaxy
needs the strength of us miners!
It needs us now more than ever!
Then tell us this. Kwana.
Why should we get involved?
What does that galaxy's war
have to do with us Asteroid Diggers?
You're right.
If you spend your life inside this rock.
then you don't have to worry
about the rest of the galaxy.
Fine!
But then it will only be a matter of time
before Nawaam comes for us.
So what? That doesn't change the fact
that we don't stand a chance
against Nawaam. He's too powerful.
This man right here
is brave enough to do it!
And he's traveled far to do so!
And I could not be prouder
to call him brother!
[grunting]
-[Kwana] And I will follow him!
-[gasps]
Because... helping each other
is what brothers do.
[♪ somber music playing]
[Homen] Kara. wait.
-[Kara grunts. gasps]
-[wood snaps]
-[Kwana whimpers]
-[all gasp]
[Kwana grunts]
Listen! I used to think
the same way as you do.
That war only happened in faraway places.
But then. suddenly. one day.
Nawaam took my father away.
[miners gasping]
-Brave miners!
-[Homen grunts]
With your help.
we will be strong enough to defeat Nawaam!
-[Homen grunts]
-Please help us!
[breath trembling]
[miner 1] I will help you!
-[miner 2] Hmm?
-[miner 3 gasps]
[gasps]
I will too!
As will I!
We're with you!
[miner 4] Leave it to us!
-[miners assenting]
-[chuckles softly]
-[Kara grunts]
-[miners cheering]
[Kara] Kwana!
I'm not the type to sit around worrying.
I'll just go straight to the source.
And when we find Zhima.
I'll be able to get answers about
what happened straight from his mouth.
[Juro] Kwana.
-[metal clinks]
-Here. take this.
[gasps]
I don't understand. What is this?
It is a lightsaber forged by Zhima.
I don't want it... or your pity.
You already know
that I'm not strong in the Force.
I don't have what it takes to be a Jedi.
Having a strong connection to the Force
was something that my former master
sought out.
But what I am looking for
is something different.
What I am looking for...
are individuals who are willing to fight
on behalf of others.
[gasps]
There's no way you'd fight
as well as you do
if you had truly given up on your dream
of being a Jedi.
You might not believe in yourself.
but I believe in you enough
to give you this lightsaber.
[grunts]
[♪ somber music continues]
[grunting]
-[exclaims]
-[lightsaber buzzing]
[grunting]
[gasps]
-[lightsaber buzzing]
-[breathing heavily]
[sighs]
[grunts]
Hmm.
So this is the kind of Jedi
that Juro was searching for.
Seems like I'd be no match for him.
[chuckles] I guess not.
-[alarm blaring]
-[miner] Wh-- What?
-[Kara and Homen gasp]
-[alarm stops]
[powers up]
[indistinct chatter]
[Nawaam] Hear me. denizens of the galaxy.
My name is Nawaam.
and I will bring order
to the chaos that surrounds us.
Right now. across every sector.
mighty figures are vying for power.
[droid chirps]
[Nawaam] But how many among them
truly care about the galaxy?
How many among them aim to bring about
the galaxy's unification?
[grunts]
[Nawaam] This is a call for surrender.
Yield now. and you will be allowed
to follow my army.
[Four-Nines speaking Droid]
[Nawaam in English] All those
who oppose us will be crushed.
Our forces are ready and positioned
to take any of you on.
There is no corner of the galaxy
that my kyber crystal cannon cannot reach.
You will now witness its power.
First. I will show you the destruction
of those who offered a hiding place
to the corrupt Jedi rats.
[♪ sinister music playing]
[gasps]
[kyber crystals ringing]
[ringing intensifies]
[♪ sinister music swells]
[Nawaam] Fire.
[weapon powering up]
-[electricity crackling]
-[explosions]
[laser booming]
[whooshes]
[thuds]
[silence]
-[laser booming]
-[gasps]
[rumbling]
-[people screaming]
-[gasps]
-[rumbling]
-[all gasping]
[♪ sinister music playing]
[♪ theme music playing]
[♪ music ends]
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today